#### **PERSONAL INFO**

**©** 054-804-7997

<u>avikaufman490@gmail.com</u>

Tel-Aviv

<u>www.avikaufman.tech</u>

www.linkedin.com/in/avikaufman-b93540200

https://github.com/avikaufman

# LANGUAGES AND TECHNOLOGIES

Java

Python

C#

SQL

JavaScript

Dart & Flutter

HTML

CSS

Git VCS

Bash

#### PERSONAL SKILLS

Teamwork

**Full Dedication** 

Pursuing Excellence

Not afraid of hard work

Proactive

Autodidact

#### HOBBIES

Chess

Hiking

Slackline

## Avi Kaufman

### A B.Sc. Student, Looking for a Software Developer Position

I departed the Ultra-Orthodox community, independently pursued my education, earned a full "Bagrut" in two years excelling in English and math, and found my passion for math and programming.

Currently, I am a Software Developer at the "KoaliTime" startup and a B.A. Computer Science student at Reichman University, supported by the "Keren Or" scholarship.

Highly motivated, enthusiastic, looking for new opportunities.

#### **EMPLOYMENT**

**2023 - Present** - Software Developer at "KoaliTime" startup

**2018 - 2023** - Emergency Medical Technician (EMT), IDF Disabled Veterans Organization "Beit Halochem" Tel Aviv

#### **EDUCATION**

**Present** - Last year (4th Year) of a B.A. in Computer Science at Reichman University, Herzliya.

**SELECTED COURSES:** 

Data Structures, Algorithms, Operating Systems, Advanced Programming, Machine Learning From Data, Full Stack Development

PROJECT:

Blog application with React front-end, Python REST API back-end, MySQL database, deployed on AWS (RDS & EC2)

**EXTRACURRICULAR:** 

Pulse Healthtech Innovation Entrepreneurship Club Volunteer Tutor for "Keren Or" scholarship, Math and Programing

2017 - External Bagroot (High School Equivalency test), Tel-Aviv

2010 - Knesset Meir Yeshiva, Rishon Le'Zion

#### **COURSES**

2022 - Intro to machine learning, Kaggle

**2019** - Computer Science and Python Programing, Campus

2016 - Emergency Medical Technician (EMT) Course, MDA

#### VOLUNTEERING

2018 - Present - "Hillel" and "Out for Change" nonprofits

#### NATIONAL SERVICE

**2016 - 2017** - Emergency Medical Technician (EMT), Magen David Adom (MDA), Tel Aviv

**2015 - 2016** - Group Leader, <u>Jordan River Village</u> camp for children living with chronic diseases, Givat Avni

2013 - 2014 - Pre-Military "Mechinat HaEmek" program